# **TU-AN NGUYEN**

+1-714-878-6337 | Fullerton, CA 92831 | t.nhunhu.ng@gmail.com | tu-annguyen.me | linkedin.com/in/tu-annguyen

## **SUMMARY**

Recent graduate from the University of California, Santa Cruz with a focus on full stack web development. 7 years of graphic and interface design experience specializing in marketing materials and websites using the Adobe suite, Figma, and Wordpress. Looking to expand my technical skill set along with my strong fundamentals in communications and visual design.

## **EXPERIENCE**

**ACTIBrain Bio** 

# **Web/Graphics Specialist**

Nov. 2019 - Jun. 2023

UC Santa Cruz Genomics Institute

Santa Cruz, CA, USA

- Use the Google G Suite, Divi for WordPress, and other content management systems along with knowledge of HTML/CSS and JavaScript to design and maintain team, publication, and news pages for 8+ websites
- · Leverage news and event content to drive traffic, increase reach, and raise awareness to websites
- Design flyers, posters, and other promotional and graphic materials

# **User Interface & Experience Intern**

Oct. 2022 - Dec. 2022

Seoul, KOR

• Designed and presented the user interface and experience of a "Braincare" program using Figma and Canva

- Conceptualized a modular game with 10+ hours of content that incorporates meditative exercise aimed for adults aged 40-60 to help prevent neurological diseases such as dementia, Parkinson's, and Alzheimer's
- Researched over 30 articles on the preventative benefits of alternative forms of meditative exercise such as Tai Chi in regards to neurological diseases

# **Marketing Web & Graphics Designer**

Aug. 2019 - Feb. 2020

Westminster, CA, USA

Union of Vietnamese Student Associations SoCal

- · Updated event info, graphic assets, and sponsorships on the Tet Festival website using WordPress
- Designed flyers, banners, and other marketing visuals by coordinating with leads and other designers

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **University of California, Santa Cruz**

Sep. 2019 - Jun. 2023

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Santa Cruz, CA, USA

### **PROJECTS**

# **Genrefy** | *TailwindCSS*, *ReactJS* | genrefy

2023

- Front-end web application for searching songs' genres through the Spotify Web API
- Built a reactive Spotify song search component using ReactJS and designed using TailwindCSS
- Made calls to the Spotify Web API with the Axios HTTP library to fetch song and artist data. Computed and visually designed collected data

# Collaborative Planner | HTML/CSS, Bulma, Vue.js | collaborative-planner

2023

- · Full-stack web application for managing tasks with collaborative features on a calendar with multiple views
- Implemented a majority of the database structure with py4web and front-end reactive elements with Vue.js

# Troy High School Virtual Tour | HTML/CSS, Javascript | ths-virtual-tour

2018

- · Virtual campus tour of Troy High School with an emphasis on their Troy Tech program
- Constructed navigation and tour interface using HTML. Used CSS to create a responsive design. Implemented slideshow navigation and image/blurb toggles with vanilla Javascript

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: Java, Python, C/C++, SQL, JavaScript, HTML/CSS

Frameworks: React.js, Vue.js, Tailwind, Bulma, Bootstrap, WordPress

Developer Tools: Git, Google Cloud Platform, VS Code, Linux

Design Tools: Adobe Illustrator & Photoshop, Figma